Querida.
Talk to him.
Your dad is getting weak,
and he is about
to announce his retirement.
If you don't show up
with your fiancée,
he'll hand the company
over to your
to your half brother,
and he is such a-
Hey, brother.
Oh, hey.
So...
Where's your baby girl?
Heard she went off to work
at a fake fiancée agency.
And where's that your
busty blonde from Playboy
you usually
hang out with?
Oh, right.
You decided to remind Dad
what a wonderful
family man you are.
So you brought your legal wife
and kids today, yeah?
And, you know,
it's working.
We'll see who gets
the inheritance
at Christmas dinner.
I bet it will be me
Because...
What’s Dad’s favorite
saying again, huh?
Mom?
A man
truly becomes responsible
when he starts
a family of his own.
That's right.
Mom.
Honey, come on.
Don't give that fool
a single chance.
He'll ruin the business
and leave us penniless.
And I didn't tolerate
your father for 30 years
for this.